字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
在我打败极速并拯救了多元宇宙后
After defeating Zoom and saving the multiverse,
我跑回到了过去
I ran back in time and created
创造出了另一条时间线  闪点
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
我恢复了时间线原来的状态
I restored the timeline to how it was,
但发现有些事却不一样了
only to find things weren't as I left them.
我给我们的世界带来了新的威胁
I brought new threats to our world,
而我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
凯特琳  抱歉  亲爱的
Caitlin, I'm sorry, honey.
你所拥有的的能力  你使用的越频繁
These powers you have-- the more you use them,
就越难逆转到之前的状态
the more difficult they're going to be to reverse.
我拿了你的手铐
I took your cuffs.
这是什么大胆的时尚选择吗
Is this some sort of fashion choice?
因为你又不是超能力者
'Cause you're not a meta-human.
-我是她吗  -是的
- Am I her? - Yeah.
我看见我们两个了
I saw the both of us.
就像火力全开的震波大战冰霜杀手
Like, full-on Vibe versus Killer Frost.
是时候
The time has come
获得自由了
to set you free.
沃利  不要
Wally, don't!
你也许是为神速力做事  闪电侠
You may serve the speed force, Flash,
但神速力归我统治
but I rule it.
你只是一介凡人
You are only a man,
而我是神
but I am a god.
你的神
Your god.
我是萨维塔
I am Savitar.
-向他开枪  -我看不到它
- Shoot him! - I can't see it.
快开枪
Just do it!
炼金术师
Alchemy!
我们来跑一跑吧
Let's go for a run.
巴里
Barry!
追踪数据
-这是怎么了  -我不明白
- What's happening? - I don't understand.
战衣的追踪器一定是出故障了
The suit's tracker must be malfunctioning.
上面显示他在城市各处同时不断地出现
It says he's appearing and reappearing
这是不可能的
all over the city at once, and that's impossible.
他不可能跑得那么快
He can't be moving that fast.
如果他做不到
Well, if he can't,
可能有别的什么可以
maybe something else can.
跑够了吧
Had enough?
还早着呢
Not even close.
看  停下了  他在滨水区
Look. It stopped. He's at the waterfront.
好  我们得找到他
Okay. We have to get to him.
然后呢  他在和一股无形的力量打斗
And do what? He's fighting an invisible force
速度太快  根本追踪不上
that's too fast to track.
-如果可以  我有个计划  -不不
- If I may, I have a plan. - No. No.
-非常棒的计划  -把手放下
- Pretty good plan. - Put your hand down.
这是个数量的问题  因为现在
It's a question of numbers. 'Cause right now,
看上去是一对一
it seems to be one against one.
要是三对一呢
What if there were three against one?
知道我什么意思吗
Do you know what I'm saying?
西斯科  你可以打开缺口
Cisco, you can open a breach
把你俩都送去滨水区
and get you both to the waterfront.
大伙们  我不行  太危险了
Guys, I can't. It's too dangerous.
我求你了  拜托
I'm begging you. Please.
还活着吗
Still alive down there?
你只是我王座下的一个影子
You are only a shadow beneath my throne.
你属于过去
You are the past,
而我...
whereas I--
我是未来的闪电侠
I am the future Flash.
我看不到它
I can't see it!
冻住那儿就行
Just do it!
天呐
Oh, boy.
明天我还是会头痛
I'm gonna feel that tomorrow.
这样用我的超能力真是新奇又痛苦
That was a new and painful use of my powers.
你还好吗
You okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm okay.
就是冷
Just cold.
谢谢你们赶来
Thanks for coming.
闪电侠
第三季
第七集
巴里  你已经在痊愈了
Barry, you're already healing.
你应该很快就会好的
You should be fine soon.
西斯科  我给你大脑做的磁共振扫描显示
Cisco, the MRI I did of your brain shows
毛细血管形态的变化
changes in the capillary morphology
和轻度中风类似
similar to that of a mini-stroke.
我劝你近期别再这样打开
I wouldn't try an intra-dimensional breach
维度内部的缺口
like that anytime soon.
好吧  轻度中风
Okay, okay. Mini-stroke?
你不能这么含糊地解释
You can't just gloss over that like that.
好吗  到底是什么意思
Okay? What does that-- what does that mean?
这个偏头痛要跟着我一辈子吗
Am I gonna have this migraine for the rest of my life?
意思是你吃几颗止痛药就会好了
It means you should take a few aspirin and you'll be fine.
下次先说这一句
Well, just lead with that next time.
凯特  我知道你使用超能力冒的风险不小
Cait, I know what a risk you took using your powers.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything.
你救了我
Well, you saved my life.
你救过我很多次
You've saved mine plenty of times.
我去看看沃利
I'm gonna go check on Wally.
好
Okay.
刚才那是什么
What was that?
在滨水区结冰的是什么东西
That frozen thing at the waterfront?
我不知道
I don't know.
但现在我们知道炼金术师只是跟班
But now we know Alchemy is just the lackey.
不管是什么  那才是我们要对抗的敌人
Whatever that thing was, it's what we're really up against.
问题是  只有你才能看到他吗
Question: you're the only one who can see him?
为什么  为什么
Why? I mean...why?
你们俩都是极速者
You're both speedsters.
也许是这个原因
Maybe it has something to do with that.
也许吧  但我觉得他不止是个极速者
Maybe. But I think he's more than a speedster.
当他抓到我的时候
I mean, when he had me,
感觉我们不像是在移动
it wasn't like we were even moving;
而像是
it was just like,
砰的一声  我们立刻去了别的地方
"Bam," we were instantly somewhere different,
即使从我的角度来看
even from my perspective.
他还说了什么吗
Did he say anything else?
他说他叫萨维塔
He said his name was Savitar.
印度教的移动之神
Hindu god of motion.
什么  你怎么知道
What? How do you know that?
填字游戏巫师  补充说明  在两个星球上都有
Crossword puzzle wizard. On two planets, I might add.
十二次交叉  七个字母  就是萨维塔
12 across, 7 letters. Savitar. Bam.
印度教的移动之神
Hindu god of motion.
-他说他是神  -好极了
- He said he was God. - That's-- that's nice.
一点也不吓人
That's not scary... at all.
-你真的没事吗  -我没事
- You sure you're okay? - Yeah, I'm okay.
你怎么样
How are you?
有什么情况吗
Can you tell anything?
沃利还活着
Wally's alive in there,
但是他的生命体征真的很微弱
but his vitals are really subdued.
脑功能也很虚弱
His brain function is low.
状况和昏迷的病人一样
Something like you'd see in a coma patient.
获得超能力后  我也陷入过昏迷
I was in a coma after I got my powers.
也许这是类似的过程
Maybe it's a similar process.
我们能把他弄出来吗
Can we take him out?
当毛毛虫处于虫茧阶段
When a caterpillar is in its chrysalis,
它会把自己的身体分解成酶汤
it literally breaks its body down into enzyme soup
然后重新复原成蝴蝶
before rebuilding as a butterfly.
如果这个茧正在对沃利做同样的事
If this cocoon is doing the same thing to Wally,
我只是...  我不知道
I just-- I don't know.
你说得对  你不知道
You're right. You don't know.
我们都不知道茧里到底是怎么回事
None of us knows a damn thing about what's going on in there.
站在这听你们说  我觉得就像是个傻子
And I feel like a fool just standing here listening.
-爸  -我之前说过
- Dad? - Look, I've said it before:
我学过的知识没有你们大多数人多
I don't have the education most of you had.
我们在这里使用的科学  我大部分都不明白
The science of what we do here is mostly lost on me.
但是我有我的侦查技能
But what I do have is my detective skills
以及直觉
and my instinct,
可一次又一次
and time and time again,
我都没用这些技能
I don't use them
因为你们全都告诉我
because you guys all tell me
一切都会好的
that everything is gonna be okay.
现在一切都不好
Everything is not okay.
很抱歉  乔
I'm sorry, Joe.
我知道
I know you are.
但我不能光站在这里
But I can't just stand here.
我的直觉告诉我需要做点什么
My gut is telling me I need to do something.
这不是你的错
This is not your fault.
就是我的错
Yeah, it is.
中城警局
没有你朋友和那花哨的袍子就不行了吧
Not so tough without your friends and your fancy robe.
我想要了解炼金术师
I want to know about Alchemy.
他做些什么  怎么做到的
What he does, how he does it--
他的力量超越人类的理解
His powers are beyond human understanding.
-试着告诉我  -你会知道的[被审判的]
- Try me. - Oh, you will be tried.
你们所有人
All of you.
当我的主人崛起  整个人类都会被审判
When my master rises, the human race will be judged.
从我的角度看  你们的结局可不会太好
From where I'm sitting, you will not fare very well.
你以为我逗你玩呢
You think I'm playing with you?
我儿子变成了那种蚕茧
My son is in one of those cocoons,
你必须告诉我怎么把他弄出来
and you're gonna tell me how to get him out.
快说
Now talk!
走开
Go away!
凯特琳  怎么了
Caitlin, what is it?
是沃利
It's Wally.
他从那东西里出来了  他没事
He's out of that thing. He's fine.
-他没出问题吗  -是啊  他没事
- And he's okay? - Yeah. He's fine.
我保证
I promise.
谢天谢地  谢谢你  凯瑟琳
Thank God. Thank you, Caitlin.
你应该去看看他
You should probably go see him.
好的
Yeah.
炼金术师在哪
Where is Alchemy?
告诉我炼金术师在哪
Tell me where Alchemy is.
我感受到你非常恐惧
I sense great fear in you.
你害怕你的力量
You fear your power,
害怕你的伟大
your own greatness.
我什么都不害怕了
I don't fear anything anymore.
炼金术师在哪
Where is Alchemy?
我唯一害怕的只有炼金术师的主人
The only one I fear is that whom Alchemy serves,
黑暗之王萨维塔
the dark lord Savitar.
也许你该开始害怕我了
Maybe it's time you started fearing me.
不不  不要
No, no, no--aah!
谁在里边
Who's in there?
冻住了
Frozen?
有人吗
Hello?
打扰一下
Excuse me?
有人在外边吗
Hey! Anybody out there?
放我们出去
Let us out of here!
我需要你跟我来
I need you to come with me.
等等  这是怎么回事
Wait. What is going on?
-你好  乔  -你什么意思
- Hey, Joe. - What do you mean?
凯特琳过来警局  她说沃利出来了
Caitlin came by the precinct. She said that Wally was out
而且他没事
and that he was okay.
什么  我都没看到她离开
What? I didn't even see her leave.
特警部队需要从费尔蒙特6号大道
SWAT needs to establish a cordon at 6th and Fairmont
到格里森建立一道封锁线
all the way down to Gleason.
走  走  行动起来
Move. Move! Let's go!
帕特森警探  发生了什...
Detective Patterson? Hey. What's--
正好是我想找的人
Just the man I want to see.
你那小朋友可有大麻烦了  艾伦
Your little friend's in big trouble, Allen.
-我的朋...  -一名女性超能力者
- My frien... - A female meta-human
袭击了警局  抓了朱利安·艾伯特当人质
attacked the precinct, took Julian Albert hostage.
朱利安  你知道那超能力者是谁吗
Julian? Wait, do you know who the meta is?
不  但是她很聪明  只能这么说
No. But she's smart. I'll tell you that.
干掉了我们的摄像头  没法确认她身份
Took out our security cameras so we couldn't ID her.
我想也许你能认出她
I thought maybe you'd recognize her.
不行  她为什么要抓朱利安
No. Why would she take Julian?
她是超能力者  他们都是疯子
She's a meta. They're all crazy.
但别担心  我们会抓住她的
But don't worry. We'll get her.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
你要干什么  凯特
What are you doing, Cait?
这里有点太冷了  不是吗
Bit chilly in here, isn't it?
闭嘴  我需要思考
Shut up. I need to think.
听着  我知道你是谁  好吗
Look. I know who you are, okay?
你是  你是艾伦的朋友  对吧
You're--you're-you're Allen's friend, right?
斯诺博士
Dr. Snow?
我说了安静
I said be quiet.
你会杀死我吗
Are you going to kill me?
-我得找到炼金术师  -炼金术师  什么
- I need to find Alchemy. - Alchemy? What?
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
炼金术师有门徒  追随者
Alchemy has disciples, followers.
我需要你创造一种算法
I need you to create an algorithm
可以让你定位任何
that will allow you to locate anyone
在过去六个月中
who has searched for a specific keyword
搜索了特定词汇的人
in the last six months.
如果我们能找到他的追随者
If we find one of his followers,
他们能带我去找炼金术师
they can take me to Alchemy.
好吧  但是"炼金术师"是常用词汇
Okay. But "Alchemy" is a relatively common phrase.
会有很多匹配结果的
It'll have hundreds of hits.
那就找不常用的
Then search for an uncommon one.
-比如说呢  -萨维塔
- Such as? - Savitar.
萨维塔
Savitar?
快搜索
Get searching.
他们不知道她为什么带走朱利安吗
So, they don't know why she took Julian?
他们不知道  但更重要的是
No, they don't. But more importantly,
他们现在还不知道是凯特琳带走他
they don't even know that it's Caitlin yet,
所以我们要在他们之前找到她
so we need to find her before they do.
萨维塔  那这个萨维塔呢
Savitar. Now, what about this Savitar--
我们先找到凯特琳  然后再担心萨维塔
We find Caitlin. Then we can worry about Savitar.
大伙  我赞成巴里
You know what, guys? I'm--I agree with Barry.
我们来找凯特琳吧
Let's find Caitlin.
好吧  你说的对
Okay. You're right.
我们找到凯特琳之后怎么办
And when we find Caitlin, then what?
我不知道  她现在头脑不清楚  她...
I don't know. I mean, she's not thinking straight. She's--
她正在转变成冰霜杀手
She's becoming Killer Frost.
就像我震波到的一样
It's just like in the Vibe.
我们还不能确定这是真的
We don't know that yet.
她妈妈说她使用能力越频繁
Her mother said the more that she uses her powers,
她转变得越快
the faster she's gonna go.
把你从萨维塔手中救出来
And saving you from Savitar--
一定是让她达到了临界点
that must have put her over the edge.
我们怎么找到她
How do we find her?
我不知道  我试过定位她和朱利安的手机
I don't know. I tried pinging her cell and Julian's,
但她肯定把他们的手机扔掉了
but she must have ditched them both.
我能献个计吗
If I may proffer a notion...
真棒  这个天才又要给我们建议了
Oh, great. More suggestions from the genius over here.
你请不来天才  天才不请自来
You don't call the genius. The genius calls you.
提问  你们怎么抓到寒冷队长的
Question: how did you catch your Captain Cold?
我在你们的文档里看到过他
I've been reading about him in your files.
好像是个狡猾的人  说话还慢
Seems like a wily fellow. Slow talker.
但他的作风  非常像我们亲爱的凯特琳
But his MO--strikingly similar to our dear Caitlin's.
什么  才不是  我们追踪他是用卫星
What? No. We tracked him using the satellite
来搜寻紫外线冷能
to scan for ultraviolet cold signatures.
懂了
Got it.
不  警察局附近没有异常
No. Nothing near the precinct.
等等  那是什么
Wait, what's that?
冷藏
食品仓库
冷藏食品仓库
Frozen food warehouse.
找到她了
There she is.
我会剔除信号  以免被别人发现
Okay, I'm gonna isolate the feed so that no one else can see it.
好的  搞清楚她要让朱利安干什么
All right, figure out what she's making Julian do.
-我出发了  -好
- I’m going. - Okay.
真是帅呆了
That...is cool.
我找到了两个搜索了萨维塔的人
I found two individuals that have searched for the name Savitar.
这是他们的地址
Here are both their addresses,
他们两个都在中城
both of them in Central City.
你要对他们做什么
What exactly are you gonna do to them?
我不知道
I don't know.
我这是在干什么
What am I doing?
朱利安·阿尔伯特
在冷藏食品仓库
带特警来封锁
这尼玛
Son of a--
警官  我们找到艾伯特的位置了
Sergeant, we got a location on Albert.
出动
Let's move.
"我会把你冻死"这句话
What part of "I'll freeze you to death"
你哪里听不懂
did you not understand?
住手
Stop.
-你走开  -你知道我不能
- Get out of here. - You know I can't.
你在干嘛呢  干掉她  干掉她
What are you doing? Take her out. Take her out.
你不想这么做的  你并不想伤害任何人
You don't want to do this. You don't want to hurt anybody.
她想要伤害别人  快打晕她
She's willing to hurt someone. Knock her out.
-凯特琳  -别来烦我
- Caitlin-- - Leave me alone.
-你在做什么  -我要找到炼金术师
- What are you doing? - I have to find Alchemy.
我们会找到他的  好吗  我们一起
We will find him. All right? Together.
不  你不懂  我不想把他抓起来
No. You don't understand. I don't want to lock him up.
-我要让他帮我  -帮你什么
- I need him to help me. - Help you what?
我要让他废除我的能力
I need him to get rid of my powers.
凯特琳
Oh, Caitlin.
我不知道这样行不行得通
I don't know if it works that way.
你也不知道是不是不管用
You don't know that it doesn't.
我知道我们爱你
I know that we love you.
我们会尽全力帮你
And we will do everything that we can to help you.
你和我  我们一起经历了那么多
You and I--we've been through too much together
不能让对方失望
to let each other down now.
求你了  让我来帮你
Please. Let me help you.
就像你帮你妈妈那样吗
Like you helped your mother?
凯特琳
Caitlin.
还是像你帮沃利那样  帮我那样
Or Wally? Or me?
你一直在搅乱别人的生活
You keep messing with everyone's lives,
毁掉一切  而我们留下
wrecking everything, and we're left behind
去替你犯的错收拾残局
to pick up the pieces from your mistakes.
有些镜子破了就没法重圆
Some things you break can't be put back together.
我可以补救
I can fix this.
像你补救西斯科的家人那样吗
Oh, like you fixed Cisco's family?
你没跟西斯科讲你害他害得最惨吧
You didn't tell Cisco that you screwed him worst of all, did you?
你听到了吗  西斯科
You hear that, Cisco?
在巴里制造闪点前
Dante was alive,
丹堤还活着
healthy and happy,
健康快乐地活着
until Barry created Flashpoint.
是他重置一切害死了他
When he reset things, that's what killed him.
是巴里害死了你哥哥
Barry is the reason your brother is dead.
艾伯特倒下了  朝她开枪
Albert's down. Shoot her!
你的小腿三头肌被切断了
That severed your triceps surae.
哪怕你有治愈能力
Even with your healing abilities,
也要四个小时才能再生
it'll take four hours to regenerate.
别跟着我
Don't follow me.
凯特琳  别走
Caitlin. Come on--gah!
-伤得有多重  -都是我自找的
- How much does it hurt? - As much as I deserve.
好  有事通知我
Okay. Let me know.
朱利安被送到县综合医院了
They took Julian to County General.
他还没醒过来  你下手有多重
He's still out cold. How hard did you hit him?
不知道  我不是故意把他打晕的
I don't know. I didn't mean to knock him out.
或许是故意的
Or maybe I did.
西斯科
Cisco.
兄弟
Hey, man, um,
凯特琳说的话
what Caitlin said--
她撒谎了吗
Was she lying?
没有
No. Um--
你很抱歉
You're sorry?
为杀了我哥哥而抱歉
That you killed my brother?
因为他原本在这里
'Cause he was here.
他原本还活着
He was alive...
直到你制造了闪点  直到你做了这些
until you created Flashpoint, until you did this.
我知道  兄弟
I know, man.
我现在都不知道如何感受了
I don't even know how to feel right now.
我只知道还没找到凯特琳
All I know is Caitlin is out there,
我们需要找到她
and we need to find her.
能行吗
Can we do that?
行
Yeah.
我黑了朱利安的电脑
I hacked Julian's computer.
凯特琳让他找到了两个地址
Caitlin had him look up two addresses:
霍桑大道16号和杜鲁门广场1104号
16 Hawthorne Avenue and 1104 Truman Place.
我本来想说她想找那些信徒
She's trying to find the acolytes, I was trying to say.
她到底为什么要找炼金术师的追随者
What exactly would she want with Alchemy's followers?
她肯定以为他能带她找到炼金术师
She must think that he can take her to Alchemy.
她想让他夺走她的超能力
She wants him to take her powers away.
我们知道  我们什么都听到了
We know. We heard everything.
好了  两名信徒  两处地址
Well, two acolytes, two addresses.
她会先对谁下手
Which one's she gonna hit first?
-两个都得盯着  -你得待在这里
- We got to watch both. - You're gonna stay here.
你都走不了路了
You can barely walk.
-我去霍桑大道  -我去杜鲁门广场
- I'll take Hawthorne. - I'll take Truman.
我很担心凯特琳  但也不想留沃利一个人
I care about Caitlin, but I don't want to leave Wally.
爸  我和巴里留下来陪沃利
Dad, Barry and I will stay with Wally.
你跟HR一起去
You go with H.R.
好  那就太好了
Yeah, I would love that.
我俩那可是全明星阵容啊
Hey, you and me-- All-Star team, huh?
好了  听我说
All right, you know what?
我去冲杯卡布奇诺路上喝
I'll make a couple cappuccinos for the road, right,
准备好今晚的冒险之旅
so we're ready for tonight's adventures.
别担心  巴里
Hey, not to worry, Barry.
好吗  我们会帮她的
Right? We'll help her.
西斯科
Cisco.
你要是找到她
If you find her--
我不会通知你
I won't call you.
你做得够多了
You've done enough.
信徒在二楼
The acolyte's on the second floor.
-喝点咖啡不  乔  -不
- Cup of joe, Joe? - No.
不喝  好吧  我猜你爱喝茶
No? All right. You're a tea drinker, I bet.
如果你就会闲扯
If you want to talk nonsense,
那我只好请你别跟我说话了
I'm gonna need you to stop talking to me.
你在担心你儿子
You're worried about your son.
-你有孩子吗  -没
- Do you have kids? - No.
那我想我们可能没法聊
Then I don't think we could possibly have a conversation
我现在的感受了
about how I'm feeling right now.
好  但是
Okay, but...
作为一名感兴趣的旁观者  我可以告诉你
as an interested observer, I can tell you
巴里很仰慕你
Barry admires you.
是啊
Yeah.
他应该听我的
Well, he needs to listen to me.
他之所以不听你的
Yeah, well, the reason he doesn't
是因为他真正的超能力其实不是速度
is Barry's real superpower isn't speed.
而是希望
It's hope.
他心中充满着希望
Kid's got an endless reservoir.
相信每件事都会水到渠成
Believes everything's gonna work out.
他这次可错了
Well, he's wrong about this one.
他们都这样  我之前就说过了
They all are. I said it before:
直觉告诉我不对劲的时候
when my gut tells me something is off,
我会相信直觉
I trust it.
而我需要他们相信我
And I need them to trust me.
下次你的直觉告诉我们该怎么做的时候
The next time your gut tells our team what to do,
我会相信你
I'll trust it.
我怎么知道你是不是只是挑我想听的说
How do I know you're not just telling me what I want to hear?
你的直觉怎么说
Well, what does your gut tell you?
-那是什么  -卫星
- What is that? - The satellite.
卫星被设定为检测
It's programmed to detect
温度急剧降低的现象
rapid temperature decelerations.
那是西斯科负责监视的房子
That's the house Cisco's watching.
我的天
Oh, God.
亲爱的  克雷格
Honey? Craig?
这里冷死了  你去看看温控器
It's freezing in here. Go check the thermostat.
-你认真的  -是啊
- Are you serious? - Yes.
我的父母都是医生
Both of my parents are doctors.
而我也一直想要当个医生
It's all I ever wanted to be.
小时候  我就开始假装宣读希波克拉底誓言
Growing up, I used to practice the Hippocratic Oath.
《希波克拉底誓言》
是医护人员从业时宣读的一份有关医务道德的誓词
我为此而着迷
I was obsessed with it.
甚至是如果有人想踩虫子
If anyone was even gonna step on a bug,
我会说  "勿杀生"
I would say, "Do no harm."
这已经深植于我的DNA当中
It's built into my DNA.
不幸的是  我的DNA已大不相同
Unfortunately, my DNA isn't what it used to be.
所以请务必相信我会说到做到
So, believe me when I say
回答我的每一个问题
answer every one of my questions,
否则我会折磨你和你的家人
or I will harm you and your family.
-炼金术师是谁  -我不知道
- Who is Alchemy? - I don't know.
我从未见过他面具下的脸
I've never seen him without the mask.
我知道他能赋予人们超能力
I know he can give people powers.
他是否可以剥夺超能力
Can he take them away?
可以
Yes.
但是你不可能强迫炼金术师做任何事
But you can't make Alchemy do anything.
他只是位信徒  和我一样
He's just an acolyte, like me.
我们都侍奉着极速之神  萨维塔
We both serve the speed god, Savitar.
他给我们展示过未来
He's shown us the future.
我看见了你
I saw you there.
你光彩夺目  无所不能
You were glorious and powerful.
主对你有着特殊的安排
My lord has special plans for you,
凯特琳·斯诺
Caitlin Snow.
还是该叫你
Or should I say
冰霜杀手
Killer Frost?
凯特琳
Caitlin!
不是吧
Really?
你还把你的玩具带来了
You brought your toys?
我希望不至于走到那一步
I'm hoping it won't come to that.
不会的
It won't.
我不会把你一个人留在这里的
Look, I'm not leaving you out here.
我想帮你
I want to help you.
只有一个人可以帮助我
There's only one person who can help me.
真的
Really?
你真的认为从一个
You really think seeking medical advice
名叫炼金术博士的人身上寻求医疗帮助
from someone named Dr. Alchemy
是个好主意吗
is the way to go?
为何不可
Why not?
我的名字叫冰霜杀手
My name is Killer Frost.
你的名字
Your name
是凯特琳·斯诺
is Caitlin Snow.
凯特琳·斯诺能这样做吗
Can Caitlin Snow do this?
凯特琳  不要这样
Caitlin, please!
腿怎么样了
How's the leg?
非常抱歉  凯特琳
I'm sorry, Caitlin.
真是冷酷无情啊  闪电侠
That was cold, Flash.
但这一下会让你更冷
But this is colder.
加速振动吧  你就会热起来了
Start vibrating. It'll warm you up.
也许我只是需要好好睡一觉
Guess I just needed a little sleep.
谢谢你们
Thanks, guys.
我现在感觉好多了
I'm feeling much better now.
没关系的  你们可以放我出来
It's okay. You can let me out.
我保证不会伤害任何人
I promise I'm not gonna hurt anybody.
看来你们都比我想的聪明
Guess you're all smarter than I thought.
刚才那一击可真猛  震波男
You know, that was some blast there, Vibe boy.
有点疼
It kind of hurt.
我没想伤害你
I didn't want to hurt you.
你真可悲
You're pathetic.
炼金术师不能帮你
Alchemy can't help you.
但我保证我们可以
But we can. I promise.
就像你承诺艾迪那样吗
Oh, like you promised Eddie?
还有像承诺罗尼那样吗
And like you promised Ronnie?
对于一个英雄来说  闪电侠
You know, for a hero, Flash,
你让你身边很多人去送死
you sure let a lot of people around you die.
这不是你在说话  是超能力作祟
This isn't you talking. It's the powers.
它们在扰乱你的思想  你病了
They're messing with your mind. You're sick.
我心碎了  巴里
I'm broken, Barry.
但是你会在乎吗
But what do you care?
因为你有爱瑞丝
'Cause you've got Iris.
你有你的幸福结局
You got your happy ending.
其他所有人都该死
Everyone else be damned.
所以听我说
So, I'll tell you what:
你们放我走
you guys let me go,
我让你们过你们的悲惨生活
and I will leave you to your sad and miserable lives.
不  我们不会抛弃你
No. We're not abandoning you.
我变成这样都怪你
You did this to me!
你有什么办法可以扭转吗
Do you have any idea how we can reverse this?
怎样才能让她恢复原样
How we can get her back?
就像凯特琳说过
It's like Caitlin said:
有时候镜子破了
sometimes when things get broken,
就没法重圆
they can't be fixed.
不能让我儿子变成凯特琳那样
My son's not gonna end up like Caitlin.
帮我救他出来
Help me get him out of this thing.
不  乔  不行  我们不想
Oh, no, no. Joe, no. We don't--we don't want
碰那东西  首先  我们不知道
to touch that thing-- first off, we don't know
会对沃利造成什么影响
what that's gonna do to Wally, right?
也许这种情况
Maybe this is the kind of situation
最好交给懂科学的人去解决
best left to the people with the science.
你是指凯特琳
You mean Caitlin?
拜托了帮我
Please help me.
你下来这里干什么
What are you doing down here?
我们都应该努力
We should all be working
找到炼金术师和萨维塔  想办法阻止他们
to find Alchemy and Savitar and figure out how to stop them.
而我们却起了内讧
Instead, we're fighting each other.
闪电侠队不在最佳状态
Yeah. Team Flash is not at its finest.
当初我为什么不跟你进屋呢
Why didn't I just follow you inside the house?
因为你很受伤
Because you were hurting.
你愿意做任何事摆脱痛苦
You would do anything to make the pain go away.
所以凯特琳如此迷茫  西斯科也是
That's why Caitlin is so lost. And Cisco.
为了不再受苦我们在所不惜
We will do anything to make the pain stop.
这不意味着你是个坏人
That doesn't make you a bad person.
这是人之常情
That makes you human.
跟我的朋友们说去吧
Tell that to my friends.
我最好的朋友们
My best friends,
一个像恶棍一样被关起来了
one of them is locked up like a villain;
另一个恨我
the other one hates me.
你不能一个人全部承担
You can not take this all on yourself.
为什么不呢
Why not?
你怎么知道凯特琳原本没有受到
How do you know that Caitlin wasn't already affected
加速器爆炸的影响
by the accelerator explosion,
丹堤原本不会在车祸中丧生呢
or that Dante wouldn't have died in a car accident anyway?
你不是上帝  巴里
You are not God, Barry.
这是杰伊说的
That's what Jay said.
杰伊是个聪明人
Jay's a smart man.
你不能一直这样对自己
You can not keep doing this to yourself,
不断在想如果当初怎样  你会疯的
constantly going over the what-ifs. You'll go nuts.
现在楼里所有人都需要闪电侠
Everyone in this building needs The Flash right now:
我爸爸  沃利  甚至西斯科和凯特琳
my dad, Wally-- even Cisco and Caitlin.
所以像我了解的那样坚强起来
So, be strong like I know you are.
我知道现在你不想做指挥
I know you don't want to be the leader right now,
但是你必须做
but you have to be.
我说过没了你我就做不到
I told you I couldn't do this without you.
你永远不会失去我
And you'll never have to.
-沃利  -对  走
- Wally. - Yeah. Come on.
表层控制室出现能量激增
There's an energy surge coming from the Cortex.
什么
What?
乔  你在干什么
Joe! Hey! What are you doing?
巴仔
Hey, Barr.
住手  你不能割开让他出来
Hey, stop! You can't cut him out!
我必须这样
I have to.
乔  住手
Joe, don't!
沃利
Wally.
Wally?
乔
Joe
我都做了些什么
What did I do?
这是你的主意吗
Was this your idea?
不  是乔  我是在帮乔
No. Joe--I was helping Joe.
没有沃利的踪迹  我用卫星
No sign of Wally. I've got the satellite scanning
全城搜索了快速移动的目标
the entire city for rapid movement.
如果他是一名极速者
If he's a speedster,
他现在就已经穿过半个国家了
he could be halfway across the country by now.
巴里  我们得找到他
Barry, we have to find him.
我更担心找到他之后的事情
I'm more worried about what happens when we do find him.
他看起来有点神志不清  爱瑞丝
He didn't seem like he was all there, Iris.
我不该割开那东西放他出来
I shouldn't have cut him out of that thing.
乔  我  我们现在需要一名生化学家
Joe, I--what we need right now is a biochemist.
你得跟她谈谈  巴仔
You've got to go talk to her, Barr.
好吧
All right.
我们需要你的帮助  凯特琳
We need your help, Caitlin.
沃利  他...
Wally--he's--
他从茧里出来了  但他的生化体征
he's out of the cocoon, but his biochemistry
全都紊乱了  他失踪了
is all out of whack. He went AWOL.
所以呢
So?
所以我们找到他后需要你的帮助
So, when we find him, he's gonna need your help.
他需要你的医学知识和
He's gonna need your medical expertise,
你对付超能力者的经验
your experience with metas.
他需要医学博士凯特琳·斯诺
What he needs is Caitlin Snow, MD.
所以你就来试着说服我吗
So, you came to try and talk some sense into me.
不是
No.
我来是放你走的
I came to let you go.
安全监控
对聪明人来说
For a smart guy,
这是个极为愚蠢的决定
that was an awfully dumb move.
我说过了  你自由了
Like I said, you're free to go.
你在打什么算盘
What's the catch?
你得杀了我
You have to kill me.
-他想干什么  -我不知道
- What is he doing? - I don't know.
不会有事的
It's gonna be all right.
你想打架吗  闪电侠
You want to fight, Flash?
不想  我不会和你打的
No. I'm not gonna fight you.
但只有杀了我
But if you want to leave this room,
你才能离开这个房间
you're gonna have to kill me.
-别以为我不会  -那就动手吧
- Don't think I won't. - Then do it.
你还等什么
What are you waiting for?
你在纠结什么
What's the big deal?
动手吧  做个名副其实的冰霜杀手
Come on. Live up to your name, Killer Frost.
让我见识一下你大开杀戒
I want to see some killing.
你想当坏人吗
You want to be the villain?
坏人都这么做  杀了自己的朋友
This is what they do. They kill their friends,
因为他们什么都不在乎了  对吗
because nothing matters to them anymore, right?
对吗
Right?
动手吧
Come on.
杀了我  凯特琳
Kill me, Caitlin.
你下不了手
You can't do it.
你做不到
You can't,
因为在那冰霜之下
because underneath all that cold,
你还是你
you're still you.
巴里
Barry!
没事了
It's okay.
有我在
I got you.
没事了
It's okay.
我觉得提早让沃利破茧而出
I think extracting Wally early from that cocoon
让他处在迷漫的状态
left him in a fugue state.
他的神经键还没习惯在超级速度下运行
His synapses aren't used to functioning at superspeed,
所以他的思维和肌肉还不协调
so his mind and muscles are misfiring.
那这个东西管用吗
I mean, will this stuff help?
我合成了一种神经化合物
I've synthesized a neural compound
我觉得能让他的思维和身体
that I think will get his mind and body
以同一速度运作
running at the same speed.
我们只用先找到他
We just have to find him first.
他去哪了  乔
Where'd he go, Joe?
你的直觉认为他在哪
What's your gut tell you?
他小时候住的那间房子
The house that he grew up in.
他一想妈妈就会去那
He used to go there when he missed his mother.
在楔石城
In Keystone.
谢谢你
Thank you.
出
租
沃利  沃利
Wally! Wally!
是爸爸  儿子
It's your dad, son.
你会没事的
You're gonna be all right.
我们会照顾你的  好吗
We're gonna take care of you, okay?
爸爸
Dad.
要命  他跑得有多快
Damn. How fast is he going?
比巴里当初跑得要快
Faster than Barry could at the beginning.
我...
I, uh--
我只是想...
I just wanted to--
没事的
It's okay.
你那时吓到我了
You scared me for a second,
简直像龙母的发型
getting all Mother of Dragons on me with that hair.
谢谢你
Thank you.
从来都没有这么爽的感觉
That is the greatest feeling I've ever felt.
-巴里  很不真实  -没错
- Barry, it's unreal. - Yeah, it is.
-我跑得有多快  -太快了
- How fast was I going? - Too fast.
爸爸  不要这么担心  我很好
Dad, don't look so worried. I'm fine.
我觉得很好  其实我觉得挺棒的
I feel fine. In fact, I feel kind of awesome,
就像一切都在振动  令人兴奋
like everything is buzzing, electric,
就像我无所不能
like I could do anything.
就是这种感觉
That is what it feels like.
让神速力穿过你
Got the Speed Force coursing through you
给你超能力
giving you power.
你现在是极速者了
You're a speedster now.
酷毙了
Cool.
接下来怎么做
So, what next?
凯特琳会对你做她能想到的一切测试
Caitlin is gonna run every test she can think of on you.
如果你准备好了
I mean, if you're up for it.
当医生吗  我时刻准备着
Being a doctor? That, I'm always up for.
但我什么时候能出任务  巴里
Yeah, um, but when do I get to go out, Barry,
跟你一起
with you?
还是用正常的速度
Okay, let's just take it
一步步来吧
one normal-speed step at a time.
别着急  华莱士
Slow down, Wallace.
巴仔  是医院的通知
Barr, it's the hospital.
朱利安醒了
Julian's awake.
他知道是我  知道我做了什么
He knows it was me. He knows what I did.
别担心  我来跟他说
Don't worry. I'll talk to him.
我保证你不会有事的
You'll be fine. I promise.
哥们
Hey, man.
我只是来看看你想不想聊聊...
I just wanted to see if you wanted to talk about--
我不想
I don't.
好吧
All right.
西斯科  你是我最好的朋友
Look, Cisco, you're my best friend, man.
我们会没事吧
Are we gonna be okay?
我和你之间
You and me?
要我对你说实话吗
You want me to be honest with you?
好的
Yeah. Yeah.
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧
Okay.
帕特森
Hey, Patterson.
巴里·艾伦  你不用工作吗
Barry Allen, don't you ever work?
我只是来确保朱利安没事了
I just wanted to make sure that Julian was doing okay.
我正准备要给他录口供
Well, I'm about to take his statement, yeah.
在这之前可以让我跟他说说话吗
Would it be okay if I talked to him before you went in?
我们的关系挺好  我跟他之间
I just--we're pretty close, him and I.
进去吧  别太久
Yeah. Go ahead. Just make it quick.
我会的  谢谢
Always. Thank you.
来医院探望  没想到你这么想念我
A hospital visit. I didn't think you missed me that much.
医生怎么说
What did the doctors say?
脑震荡和冻伤
Concussion and frostbite,
我过几天就会没事了
but I'll be dandy in a few days.
这是个好消息  很高兴你没事
That's good news. I'm glad you're gonna be all right.
尽管我很感激
Yes, and as much as I appreciate
你坦诚的关心
your outburst of emotion,
你我都知道你来这里的真正目的
I think we both know the real reason you're here.
你的朋友凯特琳·斯诺
Your friend Caitlin Snow.
是个超能力者
She's a meta,
而且不是善类
and not one of the friendly ones.
你知道吗
Did you know?
她生病了  朱利安
She's sick, Julian.
她非常危险
She is a bloody menace.
朱利安
Julian--
我知道你认为拥有超能力
Man, I know that you think that getting powers is
是对立的  不是善类就是恶类
this binary game, that you're either good or evil,
但生活不是如此  超能力者也是
but life isn't like that, even for Metas.
凯特琳是个好人
Look. Caitlin--she's a good person.
我求你不要揭发她
I'm begging you，don't turn her in.
你要我做什么都可以
I will do anything you want,but
但请不要揭发她
please don't do this to her.
我被袭击得很严重
I got hit pretty hard,
我完全看不清
and I don't have the foggiest
是谁绑架我的
who even kidnapped me at all.
谢谢你  老兄
Thank you, man.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你可以为我做一件事  伙计
There is one thing you can do for me, mate.
悉听尊便
Anything.
辞职
Quit.
什么
What?
马上去中城警局
Tender your resignation
递交辞呈
from the Central City Police Department,
立即生效
effective immediately.
我可以不管你无故缺勤
I can overlook the unexplained absences,
或经常违反规章
the constant disregard for the rules and regulations,
但你已经没有道德原则  伙计
but your moral compass is broken, my friend.
我坚定地拒绝
I point-blank refuse
与善恶感
to work with someone whose sense of right or wrong is
无常如天气
as flippant as the weather,
认为友情大于正义的人合作
someone who thinks friendship is more important than justice.
你没资格当犯罪现场鉴证员
You are unfit to be CSI.
巴里·艾伦没资格当执法人员
Barry Allen has no place in law enforcement.
你要跟我达成协议
Now, do we have an agreement,
还是要外面的警探找上她
or would you like the detective to meet that girl?
好
All right.
你可以跟他谈了
He's all yours.
艾伯特
Hey, Albert.
可以提供我那个超能力者的线索吗
So, what can you tell me about our--our meta friend?
我不太记得了
I don't really remember anything.
说实话  挺模糊的
To be honest with you, it's all a bit of a blur, so...
辛格刚刚告诉我们了
We just heard from Singh.
你辞职了  怎么回事
You quit? What--what is going on?
我...
I, um...
我真的别无他选
didn't really have a choice.
你为什么别无他选
What do you mean, you didn't have a choice?
朱利安
Julian.
你辞职  他就不揭发凯特琳
You quit, he keeps his mouth shut about Caitlin.
真是个混蛋
That son of a bitch.
我不知道  他说我不能
I don't know. I mean, he said I couldn't
既保护凯特琳
do something like protect Caitlin
又当个优秀的鉴证员
and still be a good CSI,
也许他说得对
and maybe he's right.
不  他错了
No, he's not.
巴里  你是了不起的鉴证员
Barry, you are an incredible CSI,
这个警局里没有任何人
and no one in this building cares more
比你更想帮人维护正义
about helping people find justice than you.
这是在你成为闪电侠之前
And that was long before you were The Flash.
这间实验室  是你的生活
This lab--it's your life.
你们是我的生活
You're my life.
你们两个
Both of you.
还有沃利和凯特琳
And Wally and Caitlin,
西斯科
Cisco.
过去几个月让我认识到
If these past few months have taught me anything,
为了保护你们的安全
it's that I would give up everything I have
我可以放弃我的一切
to keep you all safe.
绝不后悔
No regrets.
每次我以为你
Every time I think you've
已经以种种方式展现了自己英雄的一面
run out of ways to be a hero,
你却以另外一种方式成就了英雄
you show me another one.
-你饿了吗  -饿了
- You hungry? - Yeah.
我们回去吧
Yeah, let's get out of here.
朱利安
Julian.
Julian!
不  离我远点
No. Stay away.
不  朱利安  你逃脱不了的
No, Julian. You can't get away.
不管你在哪我都能找到你
There's nowhere I won't find you.
唯有一起合作
Only together
才能迎来我的回归
can we bring about my return.
再一次成为我的仆人
Become my servant once more.
成为炼金术师
Become Alchemy.